vizify.com 2012-05-05

# Privacy Policy || Vizify

**Our commitment to your privacy**

SteamFunk Labs Inc., a Delaware corporation d/b/a Vizify ("Vizify"), respects your individual privacy. Our privacy policy documents our adherence to industry standards for the protection of your personal information. 

**Scope of the Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy covers Vizify's treatment of personally identifiable information that may be collected while you are on the Vizify site, when you order its products, use its services or that is shared with Vizify by its business partners. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies not owned or controlled by Vizify or to people whom Vizify does not employ or manage, nor does it address non-personally identifiable information. The policy specifically addresses the following areas: 

  * What personally identifiable information is collected by Vizify or by any third party through our site; 
  * How Vizify uses this information; 
  * With whom Vizify may share this information; 
  * What choices are available to you as a user of the site with respect to collection, use and distribution of the information; 
  * What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control; and 
  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

**Information Collection and Use**

Vizify is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Vizify may collect information from you at two different stages. First, we collect anonymous, aggregate information from all visitors to the site. This information is never linked to any personally identifiable information and is only used in the aggregate to generate statistical reports about the use of our site. Second, Vizify collects personally identifiable information when you create a Vizify account and/or when you utilize certain Vizify services. Online account creation may require you to submit some or all of the following personal information: name, address, company information, email address, and phone number. For purposes of billing, you may need to provide your credit card type, number, expiration date and billing address for the card. Certain personally identifiable information is required if you subscribe to a Vizify newsletter, or sign up to participate in a promotion, sweepstake or survey through the site. Vizify may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.  Additional terms and conditions related to our use of your personally identifiable information can be found in Vizify's Terms of Services which terms are incorporated herein by this reference. 

**Personal Information of Children Under 13**

Vizify complies with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) and the FTC's Rule interpreting COPPA (16 CFR § 512). This site is not directed to children and does not knowingly collect any personally identifiable information form children under 13 years of age. 

**Your Disclosures to Third Parties**

To the extent you include personal data in your submissions (such as your email address, phone number or photo of yourself), third parties may be able to identify you, associate you with your user account, and contact you. Please do not include information in your submissions that you expect to keep private. Please also note that the personal messages you send or receive using any website personal messaging feature, if available, are only private to the extent that you and the sender/recipient keep them private. For example, we do not have any control over whether a recipient of one of your personal messages publicly posts the contents of such a message. 

**Use of Your Personal Information**   
Our primary goal in collecting information from you is to provide you with a smooth, efficient and customized experience while using our site and to allow us to provide products and services to you.  Vizify will never give your information to, or share your information with, any third party not affiliated with or owned by Vizify, except as permitted by law. Vizify will send personally identifiable information about you to other companies or people when: 

  * We have your consent to share the information; 
  * We need to share your information to provide the products or services you have requested; 
  * We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Vizify to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us); or 
  * We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process or find that your actions on our web site violate the Vizify Terms of Service or any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services. 

_Profile_   
We store information that we collect through cookies and log files to create a profile of our customers. A profile is stored information detailing how individual customers use the site. Collected information in a profile is tied to the customer's personally identifiable information. However, your profile is used solely for internal purposes, to help us improve the experience of our customers. We do not share your profile with any third parties. 

_Cookies_   
A cookie is a small text file stored on the customer's hard drive for an extended period of time. The cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Allowing a cookie to remain on your computer makes it easier for you to log in to and use the site. 

_Log files_   
Log files record internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser types, internet service provider (ISP) referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track a customer's movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information As Required By Law  
** We will disclose personal information when required by law, or if we have good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with current judicial proceedings, a court order or legal process served on us, (b) protect and defend our rights, or (c) protect the rights, property, and other interests of our users or others. ****

**Business Transitions**

In the event that Vizify goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, our customers' personal information may be part of the assets transferred. If, as a result of the business transaction, your personally identifiable information will be used in a manner materially different from that stated at the time of collection, you will be given notice consistent with our Notification of Changes section. 

**Links**

This site may contain links to and portions of other sites. Vizify is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites. When you leave our site or view a portion of a third party's site through our site, we encourage you to read the privacy statements of each such site. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Vizify. 

**Security**

Wherever your personal information may be held within Vizify or on its behalf, we intend to take commercially reasonable and appropriate steps to protect the personal information that you share with us from unauthorized access or disclosure. However, given the nature of the Internet and the fact that network security measures are not infallible, we cannot guarantee the security of your information. We use encryption to protect sensitive information online. The servers that store your personally identifiable information are housed in a secure environment. Finally, we also make an effort to protect your information off-line. 

When registering for access to a secure area of the site, we may ask you to select a username and password. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. We will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. Also, remember to sign out of the registered site and close your browser window when you have finished your work. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence when accessing your computer. 

**Correcting, Updating, Deleting and Deactivating Personal Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may contact us to correct, update or delete and deactivate our record of your personally identifiable information.                       ****

**Notification of** **Changes**

Vizify may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes, we will prominently post a notice on this page to alert you of the change. 

**Your California Privacy Rights**

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customers who are California residents to request that Vizify not share their personal data with third parties for such parties' direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, send an e-mail with "California Privacy" in the subject line to policy@vizify.com 

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at [policy@vizify.com](mailto:policy@vizify.com)
